crs-uk.biz 2015-06-27

# CRS Uk - CRS UK Privacy Policy - Used Refurbished PC or Used Refurbished Laptop, reuse of exlease PC and Laptops

CRS UK Limited (hereinafter referred to as "CRS UK " "us" "we" or "our") is committed to respecting your privacy and to complying with applicable data protection and privacy laws. You can visit our websites without disclosing any personally identifiable information about yourself (although please note that we may use cookies and collect other non-personally identifiable information about your browsing activity - see below for more information).

If you do submit personal information by ordering products, or services, for example, you can be assured that we will use your personal information only to support your continuing relationship with CRS UK .

We have provided this Privacy Policy Statement to help you understand how we collect, use and protect your information when you visit our website and when you generally use our products and services. We wish to help you make informed decisions, so please take a few moments to read the sections below and learn how we may use your personal information.

You should read this notice in conjunction with the Terms & Conditions of use for CRS UK Web.

 **Personal Information Collection**

We endeavour to collect and use your personal information only with your knowledge and consent and typically when you order and subsequently use products and services, make customer enquiries, register for information or other services, request product information, submit a job application or when you respond to communications from us (such as questionnaires or surveys).

The type of personal information we may collect could include, for example, your name and postal address, date of birth, gender, telephone and fax numbers, email address, and credit/debit card information; lifestyle and other information collected on registration or through surveys. If you choose to provide us with personal information it will be used in support of the intended purposes stated at the time at which it was collected, and subject to any preferences indicated by you.

 **Non-personally Identifying Information**

We may also collect non-personally identifying information about your visit to our website based on your browsing activities. This information may include the pages you browse and products and services viewed or ordered for example. This helps us to better manage and develop our sites, to provide you with a more enjoyable, customised service and experience in the future, and to help us develop and deliver better products and services tailored to your individual interests and needs.

 **How will we use your information?**

We may use your information for a number of purposes which includes: processing your orders and managing and administering your account; delivering any services, products or information requested by you; responding to complaints or account enquiries; administering debt recoveries; verifying your identity when required (you may lose your password or security information for example, and we may then need to ask you for other 'identifiable' information to protect your data from unauthorised access).

 **When will we disclose your information to others?**

We will not disclose information about you or your account to a third party.

For the purposes of this Privacy Policy Statement, "CRS UK" means Computer Remarketing Services Ltd.

Please note that CRS UK does not sell or pass your personal information to third parties unless it is necessary to deliver the products and services ordered or used by you. For example, we may disclose your data to a credit card company to validate your credit card details and obtain payment when you buy a phone or other product or service.

CRS UK may also be obliged to disclose your personal information to meet any legal or regulatory requirements or obligations in accordance with applicable law.

 **Cookies**

We may use cookies to record details such as a user identity and general registration details on your PC. This helps us recognise you on subsequent visits so that you don't have to re-enter your registration details each time you visit us and allows us to carry out those activities mentioned in the above section "non-personally identifying information".

Depending upon the type of browser you are using, you may be able to configure your browser so that: (i) you are prompted to accept or reject cookies on an individual basis or (ii) you may be able to prevent your browser from accepting any cookies at all. You should refer to the supplier or manufacturer of your web browser for specific details about cookie security.
